(Amy:)Professor Tupperman is dead
and that makes us?
(Sheldon:)Sad.
(Amy:)The fact that there are so many people here
doesn't make us cranky and claustrophobic.
(Amy:)- It makes us?
- Glad.
(Amy:)Giving Mrs. Davis the box set
of Roots was?
(Penny:)Bad.
(Sheldon:)- However...
- No.
(Sheldon:)Fine, bad.
(Raj:)Unbelievable.
(Raj:)You have some nerve showing up
just to schmooze the tenure committee.
(Sheldon:)You're here.
(Raj:)Excuse me, I'm here to pay my respects
to Professor Tupperware...
(Raj:)...or whatever his name is.
(Sheldon:)So am I. His passing makes me feel bad.
(Leonard:)Well, well, well, Sheldon,
fancy meeting you here.
(Leonard:)I guess the train store in Glendale
wasn't having a cotillion after all.
(Raj:)And you.
You said you weren't coming here either.
(Raj:)I have a thick accent.
You don't know what I said.
- I'd like to know why Penny's here.
- I'm here to support my man, just like you.